Randy Faison

Richmond, VA 23234 |804-833-4359 | RandyFaison@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

 Motivated and eager professional with over 5 years of experience in managing multiple tasks simultaneously. Extensive experience in customer service. Highly skilled in communication, tracking details, and organization, along with strong written communication skills and ability to partner across departments to meet the needs of the company. Ability and interest in learning and incorporating new technology.

EDUCATION

Old Dominion University, Norfolk, VA.

Major: Information Systems & Technology.

Bachelor of Science in Business Administration.

August 2019

Relevant Courses: Enterprise Information Architecture, GUI Programming with C++, Business
Applications with C++, Into to Network & Security, Database Concepts, Information Assurance,
Intro to Information Systems, Systems Analysis and Design, Project Management in Information
Systems, Probability Decision Analysis and Business Statistics, Statistical Decision Analysis and
Management Science, Spreadsheet Modeling and Analysis for Business Decisions.

EXPERIENCE

CyberClean Systems; Richmond, VA. (December 2019-current)

Robotics Applications Engineer

- Travel out-of-state to client sites.
- Test and replace internal robot hardware, maintain robotic equipment for effective performance.
- Maintaining and modifying equipment to ensure that it is safe, reliable and efficient.
- Testing, evaluating, modifying and re-testing parts.
- Providing technical advice for clients.
- Measuring the performance of Robotic equipment.
- Train clientele's essential personnel how to use robotic equipment.

Cenveo Worldwide Limited; Richmond, VA. (September 2019-December 2019)

IT Analyst/Programmer

- Develop, document, analyze, create, test and modify computer systems, programs and integrations.
- Design efficient IT systems to meet business and customer needs.
- Debug programs by testing for and fixing errors.
- Gather feedback from end users to enhance systems.

Locke Lane Management, LLC; Richmond, VA. (June 2019-August 2019)

Summer Office Intern

Randy Faison

Richmond, VA 23234 | 804-833-4359 | RandyFaison@gmail.com

- Accounts Payable: Ensuring all daily and monthly accounting is accurate. Audit all incoming invoices.
- Accounts Receivable: Cash & Check Bank deposits.
- General Property Management: maintaining vender relationships, streamline communications between site managers and key personnel, coordinate with President and Company owners for professional requests.
- Computer installation and set-up.

Old Dominion University Housing and Residence Life; Norfolk, VA. (August 2016-May 2019)

Night Desk Shift Lead

- Oversaw 6 team members and ensure all duties and tasks are being performed efficiently and effectively during each shift.
- Composed shift schedules for team members every month.
- Performed extensive customer service for students, staff and visitors, including answering questions and providing resources both on and off campus life.
- Served as a safety and security referral source for all residents in the building.

TOOLS & TECHNICAL SKILLS

- C++ Programming, JAVA, COBOL.
- Excel Knowledge (V-LOOKUP, H-LOOKUP, INDEX, MATCH, OFFSET, TEXT FUNCTIONS, IF/AND/OR, DAX, SUMIF, SUMIFS, COUNTIF, COUNTIFS, LEN)
- SQL, Data communications, TCP-IP Networks, LAN/WAN.
- Microsoft office specialist award for certification in Microsoft Word.
- Career Readiness Silver Certificate in recognition of demonstrated workplace skills in applied mathematics, reading for information, and locating information.

LEADERSHIP

- **Senator;** Old Dominion University's Student Government Association (October 2016- May 2019)
- **Historian/Photographer**; Old Dominion University's Student Government Association (October 2016- May 2019)
- Political Action Committee Co-Chair; Old Dominion University's NAACP (May 2017-Aug 2018)